残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
青い風が今 胸のドアを叩いても
私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で
運命さえまだ知らない 痛いけな瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使の帝世 窓辺からやがて到達
もっと走る熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
さあ、 loanをおからない攝影者です
クシキ RS あと 相確かも少年よく
あまりメカもariaを購入するみたい
さばし、本当にそれをおばす前 hehe
確かに女の術通りで
All three Magi systems have entered self-diagnostic mode.
127th routine maintenance has been completed.
Confirmed. Well done, guys. Go ahead and take a break until the test begins.
Everything checked out.
As usual, Mother's in good shape, but...
Is it just me getting older?
What? Do you want me to take my clothes off again?
The next chamber is an ultra-clean room environment.
Just taking a shower and changing your undergarments is insufficient.
Why do I have to go through all this for a dumb autopilot test?
With the advance of time comes the need for AVA technology to advance as well.
To do so, we need a constant influx of new data.
Now get undressed.
Yes, ma'am.
All right, I'm here just the way you wanted.
Butt naked and run through the wash cycle 17 times.
Very good.
And I want all three of you to stay that way as you walk through the room and board the entry plug.
What?
Don't worry.
The video recorders have been shut off.
We do respect your privacy.
Oh, sure you do, and that's not the point.
This is a personal thing.
The purpose of this experiment is to monitor the harmonics directly from your bodies without the interference of your plug suits.
Aska, this is an order.
All right, but I don't want anybody peeking, okay?
All pilots are ready for entry.
Start test sequence.
Beginning test.
Initiate autopilot recording.
Inserting simulation plug.
Connecting the systems with the simulation bodies.
The simulation plug is now under the Magi's control.
Man, that was fast.
The Magi are magnificent.
It's hard to believe that the first test took a whole week.
Test duration will be three hours.
How do you feel?
It feels quite odd.
Yeah, it's a little different from the other times.
Something's wrong with my senses.
My right arm's clear.
Everything else feels fuzzy.
Ray, focus on moving the right hand.
Right.
Data collection is proceeding nicely.
Everything's looking good.
Return the Magi to normal.
Huh?
A dilemma?
You can sure feel their creator's personality, can't you?
What are you talking about?
Aren't you the one who created them?
You don't know anything, do you?
That's because, unlike me, you never talk about yourself, Ritsuko.
No, I don't.
I only created the system uplinks.
The basic theorems in the mainframe were my mother's.
Are you double-checking this?
Yes, sir.
These are the parts that were installed three days ago.
The parts that are showing signs of deterioration.
The 87th protein wall.
With magnification, you can see some discoloration, but I can't identify it.
It's got to be corrosion.
There are slight variations in the temperature and conduction rate of the spots.
The clean ruins have been deteriorating a lot lately.
The construction schedule was cut by 60 days, so it's possible some air bubbles might have gotten inside.
B-Wing's construction is rather substandard.
Well, this building was thrown up after the Angels appeared.
It's nobody's fault. Everyone was so exhausted back then.
Well, just fix it by tomorrow, or Akari will chew our asses off.
Understood.
Another leak?
No, it's some kind of corrosion in the protein wall above this floor.
Just great. Could it affect this test?
No, not at the moment, ma'am.
Then let's continue. We can't abort complex experiments because of minor technical problems. Akari would chew my ass off.
Understood. Synchronization position is correct.
Connecting simulation entry plugs to AVA via the simulation bodies.
Contact with AVA Zero has been confirmed.
AT field will generate on two.
What's happening?
Contamination alert. It's in Sigma unit on the A floor.
The 87th protein wall is corroding and releasing heat.
Abnormality in sixth pipe detected.
Corrosion of the protein wall is increasing at an incredible rate.
It's spreading everywhere.
Abort the test. Shut off all foil through the sixth pipe system.
Right.
Number 60, 38 and 39 are all hermetically sealed.
Corrosion present in 6 through 42.
It's no good. The corrosion effect is spreading along the walls.
Deploy polysomes.
Set laser power at maximum. Sap every invasive particle.
Corrosion is reads 6 through 58. It's here.
Corrosion.
Right.
Just between 5.
Red is
How's Rey?
She's all right.
Reject the entry plugs immediately.
Use the laser.
That's an AT field.
It can't be.
Is that an...
Pattern analysis is blue.
ID confirmed.
An angel.
An angel?
You let an angel get inside these facilities?
I'm sorry, sir.
No time for excuses.
Right.
Let's cut off Central Dogma.
Isolate it from the Sigma unit.
Initiating physical lockout of Central Dogma.
Evacuate immediately.
Abandon the box.
What the hell are you doing?
Come on.
Isolate the Sigma unit from B-4.
Closing all partitions.
All personnel in the area must evacuate.
I know that.
Take care of it.
Cancel the red alert.
Canceling the alert, sir.
Very good.
Call the committee.
Tell them there was an error in our alarm system.
Yes, sir.
Daminated area is still descending, sir.
It's spreading all over Sigma unit from the Privnow box.
That's too close.
Yes, much too close to Adam.
We must stop the angel inside Sigma unit.
If necessary, sacrifice the Geo front.
Ava status.
They're standing by in the seventh cage.
We can launch them as soon as the pilots are recovered.
There's no need to wait for the pilots.
Launch them immediately.
What?
You will launch unit one first.
If necessary, the other two Evangelions are to be abandoned.
Unit one has priority?
But, sir, how can we possibly destroy this angel without the Avas?
If the Avas are contaminated first, we'll be finished.
Get moving.
Roger.
Central Dogma's Sigma unit will be locked down in 60 seconds.
30 seconds until vacuum pump activation.
So, that's the new angel.
Time to take a break, I think.
Central Dogma has been sealed.
Megadeth facilities are all occupied by the intruder.
So, how do we fight the angels without the Avas?
Look at this.
The border between the normal and heavy water.
There's a higher oxygen content.
Yeah, their preference is pretty obvious.
It looks like the place where ozone is vented in to maintain aseptic conditions isn't contaminated.
Does that mean its weakness is ozone?
It would seem so.
Injecting ozone.
Ozone concentration increasing.
It's working, all right.
Will this work?
Zero A and zero B seem to be recovering.
The area around the pipes is getting back to normal.
True, but the central mass is proving more resistant.
All right.
Inject more ozone.
Huh?
What the?
Uh-oh.
It's not shrinking.
Something's wrong.
Heat levels are rising dramatically.
It's not working.
The ozone's not working anymore.
I don't believe it.
It's absorbing the ozone.
Stop the ozone.
Amazing.
It's actually evolving.
What's going on?
We've got an unidentified intruder.
Someone's hacking into the subcomputer.
Ah, not now.
I'm tracing it.
They're coming in C mode.
We can't stop them.
We've got to unfreeze the barrier.
Open a decoy entry.
Decoy entry has been avoided.
Minus 18 seconds until trace completed.
Running barrier.
Barrier has been penetrated.
Open a second false entry.
Opening another false entry.
No, let's keep them all at this.
Trace completed.
The hacker's in this building.
It's under B-Wing.
In the prim now box.
The optical pattern is changing.
Those glowing lines are electronic circuits.
It's an organic computer.
I'm opening a new decoy entry.
Negative.
Too much interference.
Cut off the main cable.
Negative.
It refuses to accept the command.
Utilize the lasers.
It's generating an AT field.
No effect.
Intruder is accessing the main security banks.
It's cracking the passcode.
12th digit.
16th digit.
It's in.
It's broken into the main banks.
It's reading all the files.
We can't stop it.
It's got all our codes.
What in the hell is it looking for?
It's scanning the main directories.
Accessing codes for...
Oh my God.
It's going after the Magi system.
Shut down the IO system.
Sessor shutdown.
Three, two, one.
Quick and set it down!
The Angel is entering the computers.
It's made contact with Melchior.
The Angel is taking over Melchior.
What?
Melchior is being reprogrammed by the Angel.
Melchior auto-self-destruct has been initiated.
Overruled.
No!
It's taking over Melchior!
And it's hacking into Balthazar!
Fast!
Too fast!
It's calculation speed.
It's incredible!
Change the login mode!
Change synchronization code to every 15 seconds!
Roger!
Yes, ma'am!
How much time did we buy?
At least two hours.
I think.
The Magi have become our enemy.
This Angel must be composed of a group of nanomachines, each the size of a virus.
These nanomachines then group together to form colonies, and in a very short period of
time, they mutate in a focused exponential series to form a sophisticated intelligent circuit.
Evolution.
Yes.
They're continuously changing and adapting themselves to attain the best system to cope
with any environment they may encounter.
I understand.
It's this Angel's survival mechanism.
Total adaptability.
The only effective countermeasure for an enemy that continually evolves to overcome
its own weakness is to eliminate the host.
If the Magi died, the parasites died too.
Therefore, Commander, I propose the physical destruction of the Magi.
Impossible!
Destroying the Magi means destroying headquarters itself.
That's my recommendation as head of operations!
You're out of line!
This situation is the responsibility of my department.
Why are you being so stubborn?
This whole thing is a result of my carelessness.
Why do you have to be like this?
You never share the responsibility.
Why won't you trust someone else?
As long as this Angel keeps evolving, we still have a chance.
By controlling its evolution?
Yes, sir.
We must structure an evolution that leads to self-destruction, death itself.
We'll set it up so that absorbing the Magi will lead to an evolutionary dead end.
If the Angels believe it to be their only practical means of survival, they may choose to co-exist with the Magi's system.
But how?
What's your plan?
Since this Angel is like a computer, we could hack into it by connecting it to Kaspar.
Once we've done that, we could then upload some kind of auto-self-destruct program.
But in order to do that, we'll have to remove the barriers that are protecting the last Magi.
But if Kaspar is faster than the Angel, we'll succeed.
Yes.
This program, can it be ready in time?
If Kaspar's taken over first, it'll be all over.
I keep my promises.
Red alert. Red alert.
An emergency has occurred in Nerve headquarters.
All T-class personnel must be died straight.
What are those paper things, ma'am?
These are the developer's personal notes.
My God, they're access codes.
The Magi's secret codes.
It's like having a map to all of the Magi's back doors.
Am I allowed to see these?
I can't believe this is all INTC.
Schematics.
Everything.
With these notes, we can program much faster than we thought.
Right, ma'am?
Mm-hmm.
Thanks, Mom.
With your help, we can make it.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Rich, please.
Hey, doesn't this remind you of our college days?
Board number 25, please.
So, why don't you tell me all about the Magi?
It's a long story.
Do you know about the personality transplant OS?
Yeah.
It's a system for implanting personality onto a seventh-generation systematic computer to allow the system to think for itself.
The same technology is used for operating the AAPS.
The Magi's programming used one of the first test subjects.
So, since my mother was the one who developed the technology...
You mean it was her personality that was transplanted?
That's right.
In a very real sense, the Magi's brains are my mother.
Is that why you want to protect the Magi?
I don't think so.
Actually, to be quite honest, I never really liked my mother.
Oh.
My decision was that of a scientist.
It's happening!
Balthazar is being taken over!
Flash-Eye auto self-destruction sequence has been determined.
It started!
Self-destruction will occur 20 seconds after all three AI consent.
Area of destruction will include geoid depth minus 280, minus 140, and floor 0.
Under special command 582...
Balthazar is now invading Caspar!
They're faster than us.
They're faster...
All right.
But...
T minus 20 seconds to self-destruct.
My God!
Caspar will be taken over in 18 seconds!
T minus 15 seconds to self-destruct.
Weeds go, hurry!
Don't worry.
I've got one whole second to spare.
Only one second?
That's not a zero or a minus.
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Autonomous self-destruct has been cancelled.
Yeah!
Special command 582 is cancelled.
Mesh eye system returning to normal mode.
Red alert has been cancelled.
All hands return to first stage alert.
Oh, what's going on out there?
Oh, how am I going to get out of here naked?
Somebody help me!
Sigma unit has been released.
T minus 0-3 to magi reactivation.
I must be getting old.
These all-nighters are really rough.
Yeah, but at least you kept your promise again.
You did good.
Oh, thank you.
Mmm.
You know, this is the first time I've ever really appreciated this paint thinner you call coffee.
The night before she died,
my mother told me that the magi were the three aspects of her life.
Herself as a scientist,
herself as a mother,
and herself as a woman.
Those three aspects of her are struggling for dominance inside the magi.
She intentionally implanted the dilemmas of the human experience into it.
Actually,
each of the three programs are slightly different as well.
You know,
I don't think I'm the kind of woman who will ever have children of my own,
so I don't really understand her as a mother,
but I respected her as a scientist.
However,
when it came to her as a woman,
I hated her.
Well,
you're rather talkative today.
About some things.
The program that was installed in Caspar was the one of my mother as a woman.
And she stayed a woman down to the very last second.
How totally like my mother.
Phylologics.
Bhay Ne positon.
In other words, darling, kiss me.
Fill my heart with song, outlet me sing forevermore.
You are all I love, for all I wish you'd end the door.
In other words, please speak to you.
In other words, I love, I love you.
Will the answers be revealed?